Jensen, Vernon Longshore Research Files /4067
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Workers Union's Letters To and From Vernon H. Jensen, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Reports of Division Director, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Reports of Division Director #2, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Appendix to Reports of Division Directors, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- The Program of the School and Academic Departments, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Reports of the Division Directors, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Vernon H. Jensen's Stamp Pad, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- David G. Moore - Campus Plan, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- ILR - Cornell University; Annual Report 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Faculty Legislation, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Faculty Personnel Policies, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- ILR Voting faculty, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Maritime Labor Relations, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Jensen - 1957 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- "The Longshore Labor Market in the Port of New York", 1955 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Decasualization - MIT, and other Documents, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Decasualization of Dock Work in Great Britain, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 16)